...inappropriate behavior
in the workplace.
(Leonard:)Oh, my God. What did you do?
Oh. Let me think...
(Sheldon:)Nothing, I'm a delight.
(Sheldon:)Human Resources Department.
Come in?
(Sheldon:)- Hello.
- Ah. Dr. Cooper, have a seat.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(HR Woman:)I called you in today because
your assistant...
(HR Woman:)...Alex Jensen has
lodged a complaint against you.
(Sheldon:)So I've been told. But I can't understand
what she has to complain about.
She has a front row seat as I
make scientific history...
(Sheldon:)...there's string cheese in my mini-fridge
and that's for anyone...
(Sheldon:)...and just yesterday I led her away
from a life of sexual promiscuity...
(Sheldon:)...by making her look at pictures
of disease-ridden genitalia.